MOHAMMAD FAUZAN ALHAFIZH

+62 851 6290 2018 | zenbangga@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/mohammad-fauzan-alhafizh Cilegon

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

I am a 5th semester student majoring in Informatics Engineering at STTIKOM Insan Unggul who is looking for career opportunities in the field of information technology. During my studies, I was responsible as a member of the research and development division in the computer and accounting student association who was tasked with being a peer tutor at the HAMKA Student Club (HSC). This is what makes me personally like sharing knowledge and telling stories. My hobbies are also making websites, UI/UX design, and Pixel Art. Has experience working in the IT field for 2 years and has a high interest in technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Hardware Repair Technician, PT Star Media Teknik | March 2021 - November 2023.

- Conduct monitoring, impact evaluation activities and research related to Brand's products and projects.
- Analyzing and assessing customer complaints related to laptops or printers and Perform an initial inspection to identify potential problems.
- Replacing or repairing damaged hardware components. Handles repairs on motherboards, keyboards, displays, and other hardware parts.

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

Member of the computer and accounting student association, STTIKOM Insan Unggul | March 2023 - Present

- Setting the concept, event's preparations, targets, project trackers, team development, and growth strategies of the project.
- Become a peer tutor in HAMKA Student Club activities with teaching materials for Web Developer and UI/UX Designer.

EDUCATION

Informatics Engineering, STTIKOM Insan Unggul Cilegon | 2021 - Present

- GPA: 3.5 /4.0
- Relevant courses: Linux operating system, algorithms and programming,
 object-oriented programming, web design, network technology, artificial intelligence.

PROJECTS

LANDING PAGE HAMKA | Oktober 2023

- Designed and implemented a website in a 7-person team using HTML, Tailwind CSS, Google Spreadsheet for database.
- Create a place for potential new members of the association to register themselves.

ANTARANKU APP | September 2022

- create UI designs for mobile applications, as well as mockups and prototypes of the Antaranku app.
- create documentation to make it easier for the frontend team to implement the designs from the UI Design team.

TRAINING AND CERTIFICATION

DICODING

- Cloud Practitioner Essentials (2023)
- Basics of JavaScript Programming (2023)
- Web Programming Basics (2023)
- Web Front-End for Beginners (2023)
- Web Apps with React (2023)

SKILLS

Soft Skills: HTML, Tailwind CSS, Javascript Expert, React, MYSQL and UI/UX Design.

Hard Skills: Project Management and Development, and Hardware Repairing.

Tools: Visual Studio Code, Figma, Aseprite, Git and Github.

Languages: Bahasa Indonesia(Native), English.

AWARDS

Second runner up for Men and Women in Buol Regency 2019